(Leonard:)All right, do it.
Call him.
(Leonard:)Let's find out what this loser's
ever accomplished.
(Sheldon:)Click it with me.
(Leonard:)One, two, three...
(Sheldon:)Click.
click.
(line ringing)
(mechanized voice):
Well, hello there.
(Sheldon:)Professor Hawking?
(Stephen Hawking:)Oh, brother, you should see
the look on your faces.
(Leonard:)You really
didn't like our paper?
(Stephen Hawking:)I like your paper very much.
(Stephen Hawking:)The premise is intriguing.
(Sheldon:)Then why are you
attacking us?
(Stephen Hawking:)If you were sitting in a chair
for 40 years,
(Stephen Hawking:)you'd get bored, too.
(Stephen Hawking:)Anyway,
(Stephen Hawking:)got to go.
I promised to help the neighbor
kid with his math homework.
(Stephen Hawking:)Ciao.
(Leonard:)Stephen Hawking
liked our paper.